Welcome to the District of Waterloo.
We are part of the Sun Life team in southern Ontario.
Sun Life’s roots run deep in Canada,
where the company began more than 155 years ago.
We are in the business of helping Canadians achieve lifetime
financial security
and live healthier lives.
The Southern Ontario region
is proud to be part of that history.
Our Sun Life offices in the Waterloo District
are actively involved in supporting a variety of causes
through community events.
Sun Life advisors take deep pride in their ability
to not only help provide clients with the right products and
support,
but also to understand clients' needs
and help them plan through their various life stages and
achieve their goals.
Our team of management professionals is dedicated to
supporting advisors in this mission.
Whether you're new to the industry
or an advisor with experience,
we're here to support your success as you build and grow
your advisory practice.